let's do a little history lesson. So in 1898, this is post-Civil War, Wilmington, North Carolina was
a big old black community. All right. I know we talk a lot about Tulsa and Durham, but Wilmington
was popping. They had a newspaper called the Daily Record and an editor who was black named Alexander
Manley. Alexander Manley wrote an article about racism and lynching. It's two plus two. The math
is mouthing. Now, the Democrats who were the anti-slavery party at the time did not like
that post-Civil War, black people had now found themselves as a part of the political spectrum
of Wilmington, North Carolina. They didn't like that black folks had gotten uppity and were now
holding political positions. They didn't like that there was now a multiracial
political standing in Wilmington, North Carolina. So they used that article from Manley
to drum up support of their white mediocre base. And they got those people to run up in Wilmington,
North Carolina, start shooting at anybody who was black, massacre the town, lead a coup,
and then create intimidation that prevented any black people from not only not being on or in
political positions, but from participating politically. This was able to be done, by the
way, because the Supreme Court, even though the 14th Amendment gave everybody rights, the Supreme Court
said, yeah, but you can't as Congress protect those rights. That's what the Civil Rights Act of 1964 and
the Boating Rights Act of 1965 ended up being all about. But I digress. What I wanted to bring this up for
is because we're talking about how journalism can be used to manipulate the people.
In this case, the Democratic Party used manipulation of this article about lynching
to drum up discord that led to a massacre. Now, we know that the Democrat Party and the Republican Party
of that era are not the same as this era, but they are still political parties. And we know that them
using mouthpieces, using journalism to manipulate people in a myriad ways is as American as apple pie.
So we'll be getting to a whole lot of people from the same thing as the header. And now, we're doing
the same as theudaism that might be used to. So we'll be talking about something in this year.
And we'll talk about some of the comments as well, with a lot of people.
And we're hoping that they should look for more of their opinions and views.
And we're thinking about this. Let's see.